That is, you fought since 1914
То есть ты с четырнадцатого года воевал
and in what year
а ногу в каком году
did you lose your leg in 1915 in 1915
потерял в пятнадцатом в пятнадцатом
I understood And it turns out that you were without a leg for 8 years
понял И эти ты 8 лет получается был без
Yes, when they were beating Donbass No,
ноги Да когда бо били Донбасс Не ну у
I have a protest in the case And how did you get Well,
меня протест есть в дела А как получа Ну
what happened How did you lose
что случилось Как ты потерял
your leg  Well, here are comrades from Ukraine Well, how did
ногу Ну вот товарищи с Украины Ну как
this happen earlier? There were no drones,
это прилёт был там раньше же Дронов не
how did you
было как ты
lose it? Well, since I was on reconnaissance, comrade, I
потерял Ну раз я в разведке был товарищ
stepped on a mine and both of us
на мину наступил и нас двоих
were caught. Hello, Hello, What is that on your
зацепило Привет Привет Что у тебя за на
forehead? Yes, read it. And what does that
лбу на Да Во читай А что это
mean? We  Russians are with us God understood And
означает Мы русские с нами бог понял А
how is the name of your God
как Имя вашего Бога
the same as yours Well your God is a Jew I
такие же как и ваш Ну ваш Бог еврей я
understand I understand correctly that you are
понимаю я правильно понимаю что вы
Russians but with you God is a Jew That's right
русские но с вами Бог еврей Так точно у
you have Jews we are Orthodox Well yes God
вас евреи у нас православные Ну да Бог
Jesus your God Jesus he is a
Иисус ваш Бог Иисус он
Jew and  you are Jewish he was born from a
еврей и у вас еврей то он родился от
Jewish mother he was circumcised in short
мамы еврейки он делал обрезание короче
he is Jewish So it turns out you are Russian
он еврей То есть получается вы русский
but with you God is Jewish yes
но с вами Бог еврейский да
yes yes Yes dude look you are Russian but with
да да Дада чувак смотри Ты русский но с
you God is Jewish No no
тобой Бог еврейский
Yes your God is Jewish really
Да ну Бог у тебя еврейский правда
agree not Russian why don't you have a
согласись не русский почему у тебя нет
Russian god Perun for example you betrayed
русского бога Перуна например ты предал
your pores Look at Russian
своих пори Посмотри на русско
Look at Russian what what Show what is
Посмотри на русс что что Покажи что
there well where are the icons Show a
там ну а где иконы Покажи календарь
tear-off calendar Come on show a tear-off calendar
отрывной А ну покажи отрывной календарь
I've only seen something like this in a museum at my grandmother's
я такое в музее видел только у бабушки
when a tear-off calendar
когда отрывной календарь
is real  here is a tear-off you see a tear-off
реально вот отрывной видишь отрывной
calendar such as these
календарь такие ещё
[music]
[музыка]
exist this you surprised me
существуют это ты меня удивил
this is
это
Orthodox Orthodox yes And I also
православ православный да А ещё у меня
have an icon Here is such an icon And what kind
есть икона Вот такая вот о икона А что
of icon is it Who is
за икона Кто
Nicholas the Wonderworker there that is Greek
там Николай Чудотворец а то есть грек
understood Jewish God Greek Saint So
понял еврейский Бог греческий Святой Так
what else
что ещё
there is a lot of things show me And the balloons are
есть много чего есть Покажи А шарики
also
тоже
Orthodox balloons for the new year
православные шарики на новый го не
show me You have an icon of the Beard of Jesus and
Покажи У тебя есть икона Бороди Иисуса и
it is in another room I have no legs I will
это в другой комнате у меня ноги нету я
not go there like your legs No well
туда не пойду как у тебя ноги
I lost my leg in the war
Нет ну я потерял на войне
And what
ногу А что
happened Well
случилось Ну
war  and how
война а как ты
did you lose the war since the fourteenth year and where are you
потерял с четырнадцатого года вою а а ты
from Well, I'm from Donbass actually from
родом Ну я с Донбасса вообще-то с
Donbass And now
Донбасса А сейчас
where I am there and I understand that is
где там же и нахажусь понял то есть 2014
2014 fought and in what year
года воевал а ногу в каком году
did you lose your leg in the fifteenth in the fifteenth
потерял в пятнадцатом в пятнадцатом
understood And these 8 years it turns out you were without a
понял И эти ты 8 лет получается был без
leg Yes when they beat Donbass Well,
ноги Да когда бы били Донбасс Не ну у
I have a protest but how did you get Well, what
меня протест есть а как получа Ну что
happened How did you lose
случилось Как ты потерял
your leg Well, here are comrades from Ukraine Well  how
ногу Ну вот товарищи с Украины Ну как
did this fly in there before there were no drones
это прилёт был там раньше ж Дронов не
how did you
было как ты
lose Well I was in reconnaissance a friend
потерял Ну я в разведке был товарищ на
stepped on a mine and both of us
мину наступил и нас двоих
were caught and the friend
зацепило а товарищ
died No everyone is alive Well he also has no leg yes
помер Нет все живые Ну тоже без ноги он
Well yes I understood yes Listen and how about this [ __ ]
да Ну да понял да Слушай а как вот Сри
what do you
как ты
think  so Putin abandoned people like you
считаешь вот Путин таких как ты бросил
or not
или нет
No he won't abandon How much do they pay you as a
Нет не бросит Сколько тебе платят как
person without a
человеку без
leg do you really need this well Keep in mind
ноги тебе сильно надо это ну Имей в виду
How Russia supports those who
Как Россия поддерживает тех кто на войне
lost a leg in the war Well
потерял ногу Ну
how do I know who you are You are a blogger you write you will
как я знаю кто ты Ты блогер ты пишешь ты
post it later everything will be  it's to say I
потом выложишь буде всё это говорить Я
just That is, it turns out you're
просто То есть ты получается ты
embarrassed that Russia doesn't pay
стесняешься что Россия не платит
Well, not enough Yes, of course, it's paid, well, how much
Да ну мало Да конечно платт ну сколько
Well, I bought myself an apartment, it's
Ну мне квартиру купил себе нормально
enough Well, how much
хватает Ну в месяц сколько
does it pay per month Yes, it's enough,
платит Да хватает
I say, I won't tell you I
говорю я же тебе не скажу Всё равно
understand anyway But listen, it turns out you  you live
понял А слушай а получается ты живёшь
alone with your mom, wife, no mom, no dad, there are
сам с мамой женой не мамы нет папа есть
patsies with dad, live Danyasha
паты с папой жи даняша
[music]
[музыка]
why did this whole war
зачем эта война вся
start and why did they come here? Who are
началась а зачем они сюда пришли Кто
they? Well, they came from Western Ukraine in tanks.
они ну с Западной Украины на танках
Why in tanks? Listen, don't
приехали Зачем на танках Слушай не
tell me fables about tanks from
рассказывай мне басни про танки с
Western Ukraine.  where are you from what
Западной Украины где ты из какого
city I am from the city of Gorlovka Gorlovka
города Я из города Горловки Горловки
what kind of tanks are there in Western Ukraine
какие там Западно Украины танки там
Bezler who was Bezler you know
безлер вот кто такой безлер был ты знаеш
year Well
году Ну
I And you yourself Here you are from Beler In short,
я А ты сам Вот ты от белера Короче так
look tell me who and when and why killed the
смотри скажи кто и когда и почему убил
deputy of the fisherman of the Gorlovka
депутата рыбака горловского совета
city council Yes  I, I don't get involved in diplomacy
горсовета Да я я я в дипломатию не лезу
yeah Yes, why is it that
ага Да почему то есть получается пришли
these militants came Yes, praise the government Yes, he is
вот эти боевики Да похвали власть Да
armed
вооружён
illegally, all those who disagree, that's all And
незаконно всех несогласных вот и всё А
where is Bezler now Why doesn't he defend
где сейчас безлер Почему он не защищает
Donbass where
Донбасс где
he is not understood in Russia, he is singing to himself and that's it and he is
он не понят в России спет себе и всё и
hanging out  for your dough And you're without a
тусит себе на баблишко вашего А ты без
leg and Bezler in short, damn, everything is moving
ноги а безлер короче блин все движут
normally Well, what do you want to say with this
нормально Ну и что ты хочешь этим
and where are Strelkov? Why
сказать а стрелков где Почему стрелков
doesn't Strelkov protect Donbass
не защищает Донбасс
And to be honest  me on I'm at home defending the
А честно сказать мне на Я дома защищаю
house Well, why are all these that
дом Ну а почему вот все эти которые из
fly in from Russia yeah Let's make a DPR
России прилет да Давайте делать ДНР
Let's crush why aren't they with
Давайте крошить почему они не с
you What's your name
вами Тебя как зовут
Andronika With a ski flag Cool yeah with an
андроника Ским флагом Прикольно да с
American
американским
flag and I'm super with such a
флагом а я вот с таким
flag
флагом супер
and I have it on  there's a balcony hanging So
и он у меня на балконе висит Так что
come and take us over Listen What do you
приходите и захватывай нас Слушай Чем ты
eat
питаешься
and don't ask stupid questions and the fact that I
и вопросы глупые не задавай а то что я
eat what is already my difficulties I'm
чем питаюсь уже мои трудности я в своём
in my I live in my own house I have
Я в своём в своём доме живу у меня земля
my land and those who came to my land
моя а те которые пришли на мою землю у
they don't have  this And I live on my land
них нет этого А я на своей зем
st that's all And you also
живу ул вот и всё А ты ещё и земледелием
do farming Yes it's
занимаешься Да
easy And what
легко А что
does it grow Yes I can grow everything Well what does it
выращивает Да всё могу выращивать Ну что
grow everything well potatoes You dig what are you yes What does
выращивает всё ну картошку Копаешь что
potatoes have to do with it potatoes are a
ты да Причём тут картошка картошка - это
secondary specimen in general And what is
второстепенный экземпляр вообще А что
primary for you  there you just sow
первостепенно у тебя там просто сеешь
oats turnips
овёс репу
viburnum
калина
raspberry I I got it eat viburnum raspberry I
малина я я понял ешь Калину малину я
got it pepper nuts I have such trees Look,
понял перчик орехов у меня деревья такие
I have century-old nuts at home
Вон вековые у меня орехи дома стоят
Why to  they sent me here they want to
Зачем ко мне пришли меня здесь хотят
free me from the kolob I lived here and didnt
освободить от колоб Я здесь жил и не
grieve Yes And I received money
тужил Да И деньги получал
so look I got 10,000 dollars under
так смотри я по я по 10.000 долларов при
Yak If you want to know what you
яке получал Если ты хочешь знать кем ты
worked as under Yaniki for 10,000
работал при яники за 10.000
dollars at the factory worked tightening nuts
долларов на заводе работал гайки крутил
10,000 dollars Yes under  Yanukovych 10,000
10.000 долларов Да при Януковиче 10.000
dollars in Gorlovka you received at the factory
долларов в Горловке ты получал на заводе
nut kru what will you tell
гайка кру что ты расскажешь
a fable Well believe it or not yes a
басне Ну хочешь верь хочешь нет да
dollar was 8000 8 Green then yes 88,000
доллар был 8000 8 Грин тогда да 88.000
Green salary five was not eight but five
Грин зарплаты пять был не восем а пять
was still Hello five he was in 2007 some
ещё был Алло пять он был в 2007 каком-то
year Priyanka  he was eight don't
году Приянки он восемь был не
tell Let eight as well as ten I
рассказывай Пусть восем как ну десятку Я
got in short ten thousand bucks
получил короче десятку тысяч баксов
in short the worker at the factory never had
короче не было у рабочего на заводе
anything like that there Well I'm not only at the factory I
такого Ну я ж не только на заводе Я же
also worked part-time who did you work part-
ещё и подрабатывал кем ты подрабатывал
time
что ли
or what I just don't understand how  you can
или что я просто не понимаю как можно
earn extra money for 10,000 dollars
подработать на 10.000 долларов
it was easy to work  Yeah, and this is 10,000
было просто работать Угу а это 10.000
dollars you received like for 10 years or
долларов ты получал типа за 10 лет или
for
за
How much per month per month I understood Listen,
Сколько за месяц за месяц понял Слушай а
why did you then, in short, quit this
зачем же ты тогда короче кинул эту
job like I quit it because the war
работу как я её кинул потому что война
started well and now why don't you
началась хорошо а сейчас почему не
go work for ten greenbacks at
пойдёшь работать за десятку зелени на
this
этот
factory  so the war is already going on the plant is not
завод так Война идёт уже завод не
working what did the
работает что производил
plant produce they destroyed the
завод разбили завод
Mashinostroitelny plant what what did they
Машиностроительный что Что
build
строили
Mashinostroitelny Well what did this
Машиностроительный Ну что выпускал этот
plant produce Yes everything you want Well in Gorlovka
завод Да всё что хочешь Ну в Горловке
what did it
что он
produce And you don't know about Gorlovka
выпускал А ты что не знае от Горловку
or what I just don't know I can't imagine
или что я просто не пре Я не представляю
in short what  it was for a plant
короче что это такой был за завод что
where workers got 10,000 dollars a
там рабочие получали 10.000 долларов в
month I don't know probably
месяц там не знаю наверное со всей
workers had to come to
Европы должны были приезжать рабочие к
you from all over Europe it's funny for me to talk to you
вам мне мне прикольно с тобой
You're sitting on a
разговаривать Ты сидишь на на наком
flag behind you and with a
флаге сзади и с
trident on your chest come I'm telling you RAU
трезубцем на груди у приезжай Я тебе РАУ
Come  I'll tell you What is this
Приезжай я расскажу тебе Что тут за
Question such an interesting question very
Вопрос такой интересный вопросик очень
interesting Yes
интересный Да
uh
ээ
Why did
Почему у
n't you have any left after she came to you
вас не осталось после того как к вам
Russia, nothing, no work, you're sitting in such conditions Why? Because the war is going on, they bomb every day. Today, half a village, what village, was destroyed. You're in the throat, in Gorlovka, half a village was destroyed, Nikitovsky district, Nikitovsky district. Why can't Putin protect Donbass to this day? 3 years of his own why Well, in Kyiv on the first of the month they arranged a holiday Yes in Kiev everything the Verkhovna Rada is standing everything is working Zelensky goes to work everything to everyone why can't Putin protect Donbass Well, why can't he protect 3 years he can't move away from Gorlovka so that they don't bomb Gorlovka because these flags are yours. They are their Americans, yes. Well, why won't Putin give an ultimatum and strike Washington. Where to strike Washington? Yes, so that Washington stops transferring something to Ukraine. Well, you're sitting there, you're a politician. I understand, but I'm a politician. Yes, I understand who you are, yes, who am I, and Well, tell me, politician, are you sitting with Ukrain with Ukrainians?  trident in the
украинскими трезубца на
background I'm writing to you too by the way super
фоне я тебе тоже пишу кстати супер
write nothing to worry about I'm not against
пиши ничего страшного я не против мы тея
you we're you we'll find you anyway wherever you
мы тебя всё равно найдём приде где бы ты
are wherever you are we
ни был та где бы ты ни был мы тебя
'll find you got it got it you'll be looking for yourself
найдём понял понял ты лично будешь
Yes I'm an FSB officer I'll be
искать Да я фсбшник я буду
looking
искать
got it
понял
Listen,
Слушай удостоверение показать
show me your ID. Show me, not just show
Покажи мне не вообще покажи
me your ID. Come on, why do you need to? Well, you said to show everything. Now you're giving it a backseat. So that you can temper it. Well, don't take that last name. Well, show me that you have an FSB ID. I won't show it. I just  I warn you that you are
покажу Я просто тебя предупреждаю что ты
simply talking to the wrong person,
просто разговариваешь не с тем человеком
especially with
с которым ты разговариваешь тем более с
such a flag, if
таким флагом
you had a Ukrainian flag, it would be a different matter, but
был бы ты с украинским уже другое дело а
you are like me. Well, look, I myself am originally from
ты так я Ну смотри я сам вообще родом из
Rostov, but I live in America. I have been living
Ростова Но живу в Америке я 18 лет живу
in America for 18 years. I  Russian I've been living in America for
в Америке Я русский сам живу в Америке
18 years, look, I'll ask you a question.
18 лет вот смотри задам тебе вопрос
How many stars are on the flag? 50 as in the States, everything is
Сколько звёзд на флаге 50 как Штатов всё
clear
чётко
5, not 50 as in
5 не 50 как
the States  52 should be well count 50 And
штатов 52 должно бы ну посчитай 50 А
Alaska was not counted Yes with Alaska 50
Аляску не посчитали Да с аляской 50
Count Dani I don't need so look at
Посчитай Дани мне не надо так вот смотри
the question I myself am Russian from Rostov I have been living
вопрос я сам русский из Ростова живу 18
in California for 18 years I am a citizen of both the
лет в Калифорнии Я гражданин и
Russian Federation and the USA yes Now
Российской Федерации и США да Вот
explain to me, a Russian Why do we need your
объясни мне россиянину Зачем нам ваш
Donbass Here  look, until you asked to
Донбасс Вот смотри пока вы не попросили
go to Russia, everything was calm with us, you were there,
в Россию у нас всё было спокойно вы там
you and the Ukrainians were bombing
не то вы с украинцами что-то там бомбили
each other, and now, because you
друг друга да сейчас из-за того что вы
dragged us into this war, they are bombing the
нас втянули в эту войну у нас бомбят
Kursk region, they are bombing the Rostov
курскую область у нас бомбят Ростовскую
region, Why?  my mother in Rostov has to
область Почему моя мама в Ростове должна
run to the basement when there
в подвал бегать когда прилёты
are landings Why did we drag it in? You dragged us
идут Почему мы втянули это вы нас
into the war We are
втянули в войну Мы
Russia, don't look, you shouted at us I am a
Росси не смотри вы нам кричали Я
citizen of the Russian Federation, we did
гражданин Российской Федерации вы нам
n't need you Donetsk, we spent 8 years
Донецк не нужны были мы 8 лет
shelling yourselves with the Ukrainians
вы там себе обстреливали с украинцами
It's your problem why  you made it so
Это ваши проблемы зачем вы сделали так
that Putin would come to protect you and now they are
чтоб Путин полез вас защищать и теперь
bombing our Rostov Why does my mother in
бомбят наш Ростов Почему моя мама в
Rostov have to run to the basement why
Ростове должна бегать в подвал зачем
because Donbass is the heart of Russia
потому что Донбасс это сердце России
what Donbass Donbass is a claque the heart of
какой Донбасс Донбасс - это клака сердце
Russia is Moscow Kuban and
России - это Москва Кубань и
Novosibirsk Donbass Why do we need Crimea you
Новосибирск Донбасс Зачем нам Крым
understand no look at Crimea we at least need it
понимаешь нет смотри Крым нам хоть нужен
there you can at least relax And your Donbass is
там хоть отдохнуть можно А ваш Донбасс
dirt
грязи
What is there in
Что там на
Donbass industry
Донбассе промышленность
ra In short nothing we how many 8  years Russia
ра Короче ничего мы сколько 8 лет Россия
[music]
[музыка]
pouring here Nako
вливання вот Нако
moika
мойке
Where on the embankment not that you in Rostov-on-
Где на набереж не то ты в Ростове на
Don probably worked I am from Rostov the
Дону наверное работал Я из Ростова
Great there is also Rostov the Great
Великого есть ещё ростов-великий
And you are from there Yes in the heart of Russia and Donbass
А ты оттуда Да в сердце России а Донбасс
you understand there are all these
это понимаешь там вот эти
in short there are
все короче там вот эти
all these  I don't know Donbass is just damn I do
все не знаю Донбасс - это просто блин я
n't know for Russia Why is it on A
не знаю для России Зачем оно на А вот А
here A now listen to me that's why they
вот теперь слушай меня вот поэтому
came and thought that they
приехали и думали что нас здесь
could conquer us here but it didn't
завоевать можно а ну не
work out we don't need you in Russia
получилось нам вы не нужны в России
Let Ukraine take this Donbass
Пусть Украина забирает этот Донбасс
In short, we are for ourselves  maybe we'll leave Crimea Yes,
Короче мы себе может Крым ещё оставим Да
but we don't need Donbass in Russia,
а Донбасс нам не нужен в России
you understand You're just trying to get into our
понимаешь Вы только лезете к нам в
Russia Give you some benefits, you refugees,
Россию Давай вам пособие вы беженцы
sit here Negotiate with them there  you
сидите се Договаривайтесь там с сами
understand we are not in
понимаешь нас не вме
Russia this is Russia
Россия это Россия
Donbass what kind of interesting person are you and
Донбасс какой ты Интересный человек а
why do we need Donbass in Russia
зачем нам Донбасс в России доба нужен
Donbass there is a lot here look
Донбасс Здесь много чего есть смотри
if Donbass was needed we would have taken
если бы Донбасс был нужен мы бы забрали
it in the fourteenth year like Crimea Crimea
его в четырнадцатом году как Крым Крым
We need a fleet there the coast is where you can
Нам нужен там флот там побережье можно
relax  in short, I went from Rostov in
отдохнуть короче вот я ездил с Ростова в
1915 to 1917 to Crimea in
пятнадцатом в семнадцатом в Крым в
Donbass we don't need it at all that there is
Донбасс нам вообще не нужно что там
dirt in the tery
грязь во тери
cones Take off this cap and this
коны Сними вот эту кепку и вот эту вот
jacket and you will have Russia if your
куртку и будет у тебя Россия если у тебя
mother is in Rostov Well, what about your mother in Rostov
мама в Ростове Ну что мама в Ростове
When  Mom will receive a normal pension
Когда мама будет нормальную пенсию
Russian then I will withdraw but for now
получать российскую тогда сниму а пока
no And what
нет А что
will happen Well for now yes for now
буде Ну пока да пока
I am helping Well I wish you good luck Well I am
помогаю Ну я тебе удачи желаю Ну я
collecting for drones of all sorts like yes for And
собираю на дроны всякие типа да для И
what Well I signed you up we will find you
что Ну я тебя записала мы тебя найдём
where will you find me I am in
где ты меня найдёшь Я сейчас в
California now  I'm sitting here you can't get me I have
Калифорнии сижу ты меня Не достанешь я
n't lived in Russia for 18 years already and they burned you there
18 лет не живу в России уже да вас там
yours and it burned I have a dacha
спалили уже ваши да горела У меня дача
burned down there near Los Angeles 6
сгорела там да под лос-анджелесом 6
acres and you look no benefit even
соток и ты смотри да не у э пособие даже
shorter and work it is you sitting there
короче и работа это ты там вон сидишь те
you are embarrassed even to say that the
ты стесняешься даже сказать что тебе
state pays you you are really embarrassed
государство платт реально стесняешься
because you are not needed because
потому что ты не нужен потому что ты
Russia does not need you we  don't need it Let
России не нужен ты нам не нужен Пусть
your DPR pay you this who Denis Lin
вам ваша ДНР платит этот кто Денис Лин
or whoever he is there in short let him
или кто он у вас там короче вот пусть он
pay you money why are you from our
тебе бабки платит зачем вы с нашего
budget from our Russian budget
бюджета с нашего российского бюджета
look at us We must So stop
смотри у нас Мы должны Так хватит
feeding Donbass This is the slogan of Russia for
кормить Донбасс Вот это лозунг России на
2025 enough  feed Donbass we
2025 год хватит кормить Донбасс мы вас
feed you subsidies in short Why do we
кормим дотации короче Зачем вы нам
need you on Slavinsk still on Well you see And
нужны на Славинск ещё на Ну вот видишь А
you In short
вы Короче не
couldn't Well you keep writing yes
смогли Ну ты же всё пишешь да
[music]
[музыка]
No you
Нет вы
just
просто
In short come on let's go
Короче давай давай разойдёмся каждый на
our separate ways what what are you running away Yes when Truth
своё что что ты убегаешь Да когда Правда
eyes  colitis in short we'll all go our separate ways right away
глаза колит короче сразу всё разойдёмся
not me
не я
just not you just yes already want to
просто не ты просто да уже хочешь
run away because that's how it is Donbass
убежать потому что вот так все Донбасс
Donbass is
Донбасс - это
real Real  Russians for you in
реально Реально русские за вас на
Donbass who is fighting Russians because you are
Донбассе кто воюет русские потому что вы
all deserters in short only Yes I will serve my time
все дезертиры короче только Да отсижу
and Russians I have a classmate from
ете а русские У меня одноклассник из
Rostov Sanya Prokhorov in the second year
Ростова Саня Прохоров в д втором году
as he started his career he went as a volunteer died in
как начал сво пошл добровольцем погиб на
Donbass he is Ukrainian A drone in short hit him
донбасе ему украинский Дрон короче попал
in the shoulder tore off his arm he was lying in  hospital
в плечо оторвало руку лежал в госпитале
kadyrovtsy him there and he committed
кадыровцы его там и он покончил
suicide I am Russian alive I am not going to ponchi I
жизнь Я рус живой я не собираюсь пончи Я
still fight
ещё воевать
collect Donbass it is you who did not go for 8
собира Донбасс это вы не пошли за за 8
years you could not defend your homeland
лет вы не смогли защитить свою родину
at all you grew up
вообще вам рос
what do you want we gave you You did not defend you
что хочешь мы давали Вы не защитили вы
until the Russian guys came  for you
пока русские ребята не пришли за вас
to lay down my bones everything
ложиться костьми всё
you we
вы мы
ru We Russians do not respect you We Russians do not
ру Мы русские вас не Мы русские вас не
respect you In the fourteenth year I
уважаем Я в четырнадцатом году с палкой
stood at the checkpoint with a stick with a stick That's exactly
стоял на блокпосту с палкой Вот именно
what normal men can stand with a stick
это с палкой это то могут стоять
in short the Russians came
нормальные мужики короче русские пришли
with normal And then he stood with a stick stick
с нормально А то с палкой стоял палка
pick set you can twist this
ковырялка сеты можешь покрутить этой
with a stick with a stick at the checkpoint and then I
палкой палкой на блокпосту а потом я
left and then I left in
уехал а потом я уехал в
s and there he
с и там
gave not this you are telling all the bass fables you
давал не это ты всё бас басни
understand e for now that you
рассказываешь понимаешь е пока что вы
Slavyansk You all ran away from Slavyansk how is
Славянск Вы из Славянска убежали все как
this a disgrace nation with this whole brigade
это позор нейшен со всей этой бригады
ran away from Slavyansk ran away from
убегали из Славянска убежали из
Slavyansk surrendered  Slavyansk without a fight It's
Славянска сдали Славянск без боя Это
just a disgrace to the Donbass people how they surrendered
просто позор донбасско народа как сдали
Slavyansk is a disgrace, a real disgrace, they just
Славянск позор реально позор просто
disgraced us because A because
опозорили что а потому что А потому что
all the men were sitting and working in the mines and
все мужики сидели работали на шахта и на
factories And no one wanted to fight with you
заводах А никто не хотел с вами воевать
together, yes, it's true, everyone was sitting in the mines and
вместе да правда все сидели на шахтах и
factories And you  ran away from Slavyansk Why did
заводах А вы убежали из Славянска Почему
they run away Where will Donbass stand there Everything is like
убежали где там Донбасс будет стоять всё
that Even a
так аж
tarantula on two legs still ran away
таранта на двух ногах ещё убегал
Yes We didn't have so many
да У нас не было столько
people to defend ourselves Why didn't they And why did
людей обороняться А почему не было А что
n't the locals join the self-defense All yes
местные не вступили в самооборону все да
All the locals were just Why isn't there a
Все местные были как раз Почему нет
place How are you  once they ran away and people
месте Вы как раз убежали а люди в
remained in Slavyansk
Славянске остались
[music]
[музыка]
no that's how you ran away shooters betrayed
нет вот так вы убежали стрелков предал
people Slavic you pre in Kramatorsk in
людей славянско ты пре в Краматорске в
Konstantinovka
Константиновке
all traitors you ran away worked in
все предатели вы убежали работали на
factories in Shakhty worked in a mine Who
заводах в Шахтах в шахте работал Кто на
worked at the factory they thought that we would
заводе они работали они думали что мы их
protect them We thought that just like that these will
защитим Мы думали что просто так эти
come we them  we'll fight back
придут мы их отобьёмся
we fought them off fought them off and couldn't
мы их отбивали отбивали и не смогли
fight them off because we didn't have enough people and
отбить потому что нас людей не хватило а
then we came home they're sitting there and weren't
потом домой приш они сидят
released Yes, you ran away you ran away shamefully
на выпустили Да убежали вы позорно
We were in Russia watching we were with me
убежали Мы в России смотрели мы у меня
my mother was still saying everything now Slavensk
ещё мама говорила всё сейчас славенск
will hold out and then she says look
будет держаться а потом говорит смотри
son how these  Donbass are running away from
Сынок как эти донбасы убегают из
Slavyansk everything is worth a penny
Славянска всё Грош цена
they are
им Грош
worth a penny Yes there were as many of us there as there were a
цена Да нас там было по сколько нас по
division already
дивизия вот уже
Well so
Ну так
how many
сколько
times don't make excuses Well don't make excuses they
коло не оправдывайся Ну не оправ убежали
ran away ran away flashing their heels Well it happened
убежали сверкали пятками Ну было такое
Well
Ну
admit it No you don't admit it but you
признайся Нет не призна а ж ты
heroically didn't go in short to
героически не пошл короче
you  helped how many weapons did
вам помогали сколько оружия поставляла
Russia supply how many of ours are for you  fought
Россия сколько наших за вас воевала
nothing That's exactly when they didn't
ничего Вот как раз тогда они не
supply not everything they supplied what are you
поставляли не всё поставляли что ты
telling Strelkov we
расска Стрелкова мы вам Стрелкова
handed over to you Strelkov from Russia Strelkov we handed over to
передали из России Стрелкова мы передали
you handed over everyone handed over And you all
вам передали всех передали А вы всё
just Now you don't have any
просто Теперь у тебя нету ни короче
Slavyansk, no legs, no homeland, no work,
Славянска ни ноги ни Родины ни работы
nothing
ничего нет
I have  there is a Motherland and a leg now you don't
У меня есть и Родина и нога сейчас не
have a Motherland you don't
нету у тебя Родины нету Родины ты не
need either the Ukrainians or us or us Russians
нужен ни украинцам не нам не нам русским
you don't need us
ты не нужен нам
Ukrainians we your Donbass at all
украинцам нам ваш Донбасс вообще вот
really We want here a ditch with crocodiles
реально Мы хотим вот ров крокодилами
if I If on if let's be like this
если я Если на если вот давай так будем
with you  talk if Donbass is
с тобой разговаривать если Донбасс
not needed by anyone then I don't talk to you
никому не нужен тогда я с тобой не
so run away yeah yeah
разговариваю так убежал да
yeah yeah I love it when I'm with these
Ага дада да я люблю когда я с этими
Donbass people yeah when I'm Russian from Rostov
донбасами да когда я русский из Ростова
of course damn It's a bummer I
конечно блин Палево
got offended there's
обиделся работы
no work no stick
нет палки
Netto another stick but we are Russians
Нетто другая палка зато мы русские с
God lives with us  like subscribe comment
нами бог живёт в лайк подписка комент
write to my Telegram right now axis VN
пись на мий Telegram прямо зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very  important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg or in your ban and very
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people sometimes I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational links
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okrim video there is also interesting and useful
окрим видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry  with you
информация и мы повинни з вами тримати
three constant operational connections
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini
YouTube Слава украини
subscribe A
подпишись A